太棒了 让我换一下底片
Great. Great. Just give me a sec to change film.
我知道你不希望我知道 但我知道了 我为你感到高兴
Okay. I know I'm not supposed to know, but I do and I am so excited for you.
- 发生了什么事   - 摩妮卡怀孕了
- Why? What's going on?     - Monica's pregnant.
天啊 所以你们两个要结婚
Oh, my God! Is that why you guys had to get married?
- 听着 我没有怀孕   - 精子游得太慢了
- Guys, I'm not pregnant!     - Ah, slow swimmers?
什么 你是什么意思 你没有怀孕
What? What do you mean? You're not pregnant?
- 你没有告诉任何人我怀孕了吧   - 没有
- You didn't tell anybody I was, did you?     - No.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
我们为什么不拍张摩妮卡跟英勇士兵的合照
Now why don't we get a shot of Monica and the bloody soldier?
关于那一点 乔伊 你得在婚宴开始前换套衣服
Oh, about that. Joey, you have to change before the party.
- 我办不到 我没带衣服来换   - 拜托你去找套衣服
I can't. I don't have any other clothes.
别再穿着"我在法国战死"的衣服
Find some. Please! Anything that doesn't say, "I died tragically in France."
我们为什么不让新人跟伴娘们合照一些照片
Then why don't we see the bride and the groom, and the bridesmaids?
摩妮卡 你为什么告诉大家你没有怀孕
Hey, Mon? Why did you tell the guys that you weren't pregnant?
因为我没有怀孕
Because I'm not.
我们发现了你的验孕棒 如果你没有怀孕…
We found your test in the trash. If you're not pregnant...
那是因为我怀孕了
...it's because I am.
你在胡说什么
What are you talking about?
对 我怀了孩子
Yes. Ahem. I am with child.
我不想说是因为今天是你们的大喜之日
And I didn't wanna say anything because it's your day.
- 我不想抢了你的风采   - 于是你告诉大家我怀孕了
- I didn't wanna steal your thunder.     - So you told people I was pregnant?
这是那种我会想记住的对话吗
Does this look like a conversation I wanna remember?
- 孩子的爸是谁   - 对
- Who's the father?     - Yeah.
我不能说
I can't say.
- 为什么   - 为什么不行
- Why?     - Why not?
我不能说 因为他是名人
I can't say because he's famous.
天啊 他是谁
Oh, my God, who is it?
菲比 你得告诉我们
Come on, you have to tell us.
好吧 是詹姆斯·布洛林
Okay, okay. It's James Brolin.
詹姆斯·布洛林是孩子的爸爸
James Brolin is the father of my baby.
你是说芭芭拉·史翠珊的老公 詹姆斯·布洛林
As in, Barbra Streisand's husband, James Brolin?
什么 他一直都没有告诉我
What? He never said that to me.
# 没有人告诉你活着有多累 #
# So no one told you life was gonna be this way #
# 上班受罪 口袋空空 爱情变累赘 #
# Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's D.O.A. #
# 寂寞又潦倒 受气又受累 #
# It's like you're always stuck in second gear #
# 日复一日 年复一年 #
# When it hasn't been your day, #
# 时运不济 活着受罪 #
# your week, your month, or even your year #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# but I'll be there for you #
# 你我相偎相依 #
# 'Cause you're there for me too #
摩妮卡 请你先离开 我们要拍钱德跟伴娘的合照
Monica, if you can step away, we'll get Chandler and the bridesmaids.
何不只拍伴娘的合照呢
How about just the bridesmaids?
我是新郎 听说这个位置很重要
I am the groom. I was told it was kind of a big deal.
- 没错   - 对
- It is.     - Yeah.
- 天啊   - 谢谢你
- Oh, my God!     - Thank you for doing that.
我还没有办法承受那样的压力
I just can't deal with this just quite yet.
于是你告诉我 摩妮卡怀孕了
So instead you told me Monica was pregnant?     -
是你说她怀孕了 我只是没有反驳你
You did, I just didn't disagree.
- 很狡猾   - 对
- Sneaky!     - Yeah.
- 笑一个 小姐们   - 噢
- Smile, ladies!     - Ohh.
- 对了 詹姆斯·布洛林   - 我知道
- By the way, James Brolin?     - Ugh. I know.
我脑海里浮起两个人名 他跟小艾德·贝格利
I could only think of two names: Him and Ed Begley Jr. And then...
然后我想起来他是同志 所以…
I remembered he's gay, so...
- 小艾德·贝格利不是同志   - 真的吗
- Ed Begley Jr. Is not gay.     - Really?
谢谢 各位先生女士 我很荣幸
Thank you very much. Ladies and gentlemen, it gives me great pleasure...
跟大家介绍
...to introduce to you for the first time:
钱德宾夫妇
Mr. And Mrs. Chandler Bing!
到舞池前我要送你一份礼物
Before we go out there, I got a present for you.
我不想把手伸到你的口袋里
I'm not gonna put my hand in your pocket.
- 不   - 不吗
- No.     - No?
- 我去上了舞蹈课   - 什么
- I've been taking dancing lessons.     - What?
对 我上了六星期舞蹈课 我希望这一刻能让你永生难忘
Yeah, for the last 6 weeks. I wanted this to be a moment you'd never forget.
那真的是太体贴了
Aww. That is so sweet!
你愿不愿意以夫妻的身份跟我跳第一支舞
So would you care to join me in our first dance as husband and wife?
- 我愿意   - 很好
- Yes.     - Okay.
- 怎么了   - 我的新鞋太滑了
- What's the matter?     - These new shoes are all slippery.
- 你能跳舞吗   - 不太行
- Are you going to be able to do this?     - Not well.
好消息 我想没有人在看我们
Well, the good news is I don't think anyone's looking at us.
- 你准备要谈了吗   - 不要
- So you ready to talk about it?     - No.
现在呢
Now?
不要
No.
那我们来谈别的事
Okay, we'll talk about something else.
- 谢谢   - 孩子的爸是谁
- Thank you.     - Who's the father?
甜心 我还没有告诉他…
Uh. Look, honey, I haven't told him yet...
我打算先告诉他 再告诉其他人
...so until I do, I don't think I should tell anybody else.
没关系 那很公平 是泰格吗
Yeah. That's fine. That's fair. Is it Tag?
菲比
Ugh. Phoebe!
- 好吧 对不起 我不说了   - 好吧
- Okay. I'm sorry, I'll stop.     - Okay.
是罗斯吗 是罗斯吧
Is it Ross? It's Ross, isn't it?
- 天啊 是乔伊   - 别说了 好吗
- Oh, my God, it's Joey!     - Honey, stop it, okay?
在告诉他之前 我不会告诉你的
I'm not going to tell you until I tell him.
至少我们知道他是个男的
Ah-ha! At least we know it's a him.
天啊
Oh, sweet lord.
对不起 好吗
I'm sorry, okay?
我跑到礼品店 那里只卖这个跟浴袍
I went down to the gift shop, and it was either this or a bathrobe.
什么事比较重要呢 我的穿着打扮还是我今天能够出席
Look, what's more important? The way I'm dressed or me being with you today?
我不会假装我听到你说什么
Honey, I'm not even going to pretend I was listening. Hey! Hey.
嗨
Hi.
我是罗斯 我相信我们没有见过 我是摩妮卡的哥哥
I'm Ross. I don't believe we've met. I'm Monica's older brother.
- 嗨 我是她在餐厅的同事蒙娜   - 噢
- Hi, I'm Mona from her restaurant.     - Oh.
你好 "她在餐厅的同事蒙娜"
Hello, "Mona from her restaurant."
蒙娜 这个名字很美
Mona. What a beautiful name.
你真的那么想 我一直都很讨厌这个名字
You think so? I always kind of hated it.
- 少来了 蒙娜丽莎   - 啊哈
- Aw, come on! Mona Lisa?     - Uh-huh.
蒙娜…
Mona...
利格拉齐
...Klegglachen?
她是著名的植物学家
The famous botanist. Huh?
不 她… 她死了 但是…
Oh, no. She's... Well, she's dead now.
她曾经是植物学界最性感的女人
But supposedly she was once quite the hottie of the plant world.
- 真的吗   - 对
- Really?     - Yeah.
- 我根本不认识她   - 琳达·利格拉齐…
- Well, see, I never knew about her.     - Linda Klegglachen...
你在几号桌
So, what table are you at?
我也是
Oh, heh, me too.
很好 那么有个喜欢我名字的人会跟我同桌
Good. There will be someone who likes my name.
对 没错
Yes, there will.
你猜怎么了 茉莉·吉柏特 你刚刚被踢到一号桌
Guess what, Molly Gilbert. You've just been bumped up to table one.
如果你没有意见的话 我要代替你坐到六号桌
And if it's all right with you, I'm gonna take your place at table six.
马丁·利格拉齐
Martin Klegglachen!
那样子好多了 现在双手弯曲 眼睛看前方
That's better. Just bend your arms a little more. There you go. Look straight ahead.
这次我要你臀部用力顶
Now this time I want you to really put your ass into it.
钱德 你看 我的男伴终于来了
Chandler, darling, look, my date has finally arrived.
我要你见见丹尼斯·菲利浦斯
I'd like you to meet Dennis Phillips.
- 恭喜   - 谢谢
- Congratulations.     - Thanks.
丹尼斯是我的老朋友跟很棒的情人
Dennis is a dear old friend. And a fantastic lover.
太棒了 丹尼斯 谢谢你取悦我老妈
Bravo, Dennis, thanks for pleasing my mother so.
抱歉我没赶上婚礼 我忙着在试镜
I'm so sorry I missed the ceremony. I was stuck at auditions.
对 丹尼斯正在执导一出百老汇新戏
Dennis is directing a new Broadway show.
我不敢相信能见到你 乔伊·崔比亚尼
Hi, I don't believe we've met. Joey Tribbiani.
- 丹尼斯·菲利浦斯   - 多年来我一直很仰慕你的成就
- Dennis Phillips.     - Wow. I've admired your work for years.
你真的很棒
You've done some amazing stuff.
谢谢 对不起 我要去喝点东西
Thank you. Excuse me, I'll get myself a drink.
我马上回来
I'll be back in a moment.
丹尼斯·菲利浦斯 那真的是太棒了 你们怎么认识的
Dennis Phillips! That's great! How did you guys meet?
那是个有趣的故事
Well, you know, it's a funny story.
是普通有趣还是爆笑
Funny "ha-ha," or funny "boom, uh-oh!"
谢谢 大家请坐
Thank you very much. Now if everyone will please take their seats,
晚宴马上开始
dinner will be served.
嗨
Hey.
- 我以为你在六号桌   - 不 是九号桌
- Uh, I thought you were at table six.     - Uh, no. Nine.
你刚刚拿给我看时 是那样子拿的…
Ohh. See, before, when you showed it to me, you held it that way...
我被你误导了
...which was misleading.
我…
Well... I'll... um...
哈罗
Hello.
钱德 你能请你妈把我的履历表拿给丹尼斯·菲利浦斯吗
Chandler! Will you see if your mom can give my resume to Dennis Phillips?
只要能演百老汇舞台剧 我就什么戏都能演了
Because if I can get into a Broadway show, I would've done it all:
电影 电视剧跟舞台剧
Film, television and theater.
唯一例外是广播剧 因为那是给丑八怪演的
The only thing left would be radio, and that's just for ugly people.
- 你穿几号鞋   - 11 11号半
- What size shoes do you wear?     - Uh, eleven. Eleven and a half.
我的鞋子太滑没办法跳舞
Great. My shoes are giving me a problem on the dance floor.
你的戏靴能借我吗
Can I borrow the boots from your costume?
我真的不知道我把靴子丢到哪里去了
I don't know where I left those, so...
- 你的脚不可能是11号半   - 好吧 我穿7号的鞋子
- Those aren't eleven and a half.     - Okay, fine, I'm a 7!
我的脚非常小 但其他部分都很大 我可以露给你看
All right, I have surprisingly small feet. But the rest of me is good! I'll show you!
- 你能相信菲比怀孕了吗    - 现在别谈那件事
- Can you believe Phoebe got pregnant?     - Let's not talk about that now.
- 这是大消息   - 没错 但它没有你的婚礼重要
- This is so huge.     - Sure, but as big as your wedding?
当然 我的婚礼是最重要的
Of course not. Nothing is.
- 这是我们私下的谈话   - 是的
- Wow. Between me and you?     - Yeah.
到了这个时代 谁会笨到让自己怀孕
In this day and age, how dumb do you have to be to get pregnant?
有时候你该做的都做了 大家都戴上他们该戴的东西…
Hey, sometimes you can do everything right, wear what you're supposed to...
但有个小家伙还是攻过了城池
...and one of those little guys just gets through.
- 怎么会呢   - 我不知道 或许它们有工具
- How?     - I don't know, maybe they have tools.
我跟她谈过 她想留下孩子
Well, I talked to her, and she's definitely gonna have this baby.
她说她要自己抚养孩子
She's gonna raise it on her own.
- 或许那真的很勇敢   - 或许吧
- Well, maybe that's really brave.     - Maybe.
我只是希望她知道那有多辛苦
I just hope she realizes how hard it's gonna be.
或许她没有想那么多
Maybe she hasn't really thought it through that much.
的确有很多事需要考虑
There's a lot to think about.
她要怎么处理经济问题  她怎么有办法去工作
How is she gonna handle this financially? How is she gonna juggle work?
她知道她在未来的18年内都无法再去约会了吗
Does she realize she's not gonna have a date again for the next 18 years?
我不知道
I don't know.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
嗯 嗯
Mm-hm.
我只是想到了菲比 怀了孕的可怜菲比
I'm just thinking about Phoebe. Poor, knocked-up Phoebe.
- 要喝香槟吗   - 好的 谢谢你
- Champagne?     - Oh, yes. Thank you very much. Whew.
法国人都是那样喝香槟的
That's actually how the French drink it.
我刚刚跟我的情人詹姆斯·布洛林通过电话
Well, I just got off the phone with my lover, James Brolin.
- 真的吗    - 真的
- Really?     - Yes.
很明显地他娶了一个歌手
And apparently, he is married to some singer.
但他说他会为了我离开她 我说"你确定吗"
But he said he'd leave her for me. So I said, "Are you sure?"
- 詹姆斯·布洛林说…   - 怀孕的人是瑞秋
- And James Brolin said...     - Rachel's the one who's pregnant?
什么
What?
干嘛那么麻烦呢
Why bother?
你觉得如何
How do you feel?
我不知道我有什么感觉 一切发生的太快
I don't know how I feel. This is all happening so fast.
我得做出这些我不想做的决定
I have to make all these decisions that I don't want to make.
快把这玩意拿走
Mm! Oh! Someone take this away from me!
- 冷静点 或许你没有怀孕   - 什么
- Calm down. Maybe you're not pregnant.     - What?
我怀三胞胎时 也验了三次孕才确定
When I got pregnant with the triplets, I took the test three times.
对 或许是假警报 你确定你尿在验孕棒的方式没错
Yes. Maybe it's a false-positive. Are you sure you peed on the stick right?
不然我要怎么尿才对
How many ways are there to do that?
我是说没有百分之百确定前 别大惊小怪
I'm just saying, don't freak out until you're 100 percent sure.
好吧 我回家后会再验一次
I'll take it again at home.
- 你可以现在验   - 就当是送我的礼物
You gotta take it now, as a present to me.
好吧 谢谢你
Okay. Thank you.
- 我去帮你买验孕棒   - 你们真的是太棒了
- I'll run out and get you one.     - Aw, you girls are so great.
等一下 孩子的爸是谁
Wait a minute. Who's the father?
- 她不肯告诉我们   - 快说吧 这是我的婚礼
- She won't tell us.     - Come on! It's my wedding.
这可以当做是送我的礼物
That could be my present.
- 我才刚答应为了你验孕 - 看吧 所以一定要有礼物清单
- Hey! I just gave you peeing on a stick.     - See, this is why you register.
又是椅子的声音 好吗 不是我干的
It was the chair again, okay? I'm not doing it!
听着 我没有… 你知道吗
It was... Look, I don't. You know what?
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hi.     - Hi.
- 你想跳舞吗   - 好啊
- Would you like to dance?     - Sure.
太棒了
- Yeah.     - Oh, great.
- 盖勒博士   - 我没有放屁
- Dr. Geller?     - I wasn't farting!
那是我们那一桌玩的小游戏
Uh, a little game from our table.
- 什么事   - 盖勒博士 你愿意跟我跳舞吗
- Yes?     - Dr. Geller, will you dance with me?
噢 嗯…
Oh. Um...
或许待会再说 现在我要跟这位小姐跳舞
Maybe later. I'm about to dance with this lady.
好吧
Okay.
哦哦
Ooooh.
除非这位小姐不介意让你插队
Unless this lady wouldn't mind letting you go first.
我很乐意 你太好心了
I'd be happy to. You are very sweet.
没错
Ohh. Yes, I am.
事实上我们来试试我的绝招 你可以踩在我的脚上跳舞
In fact, why don't we try it my special way. You can dance on my feet.
- 没问题   - 是吗 跳上来吧
- Sure.     - Yeah? Hop on.
- 那个美丽的小姐在看吗   - 啊哈
- Is the pretty lady looking?     - Uh-huh.
继续跳
Keep dancing.
谁想得到呢
And the world will never know.
- 你跟丹尼斯提过我的事了吗 - 有 我说你非常有天分
- Hey! Did you talk to Dennis?     - Yes. I told him how talented you were.
还有"我们的日子"的事
I told him all about Days ofour Lives.
不…你不能告诉百老汇导演那种事
No, you don't tell a Broadway guy that!
- 他会以为我是肥皂剧演员 - 但你不只是肥皂剧演员
- Now he thinks I'm just a soap actor.     - But you're not just a soap actor.
你是有双小脚的肥皂剧演员
You are a soap actor with freakishly tiny feet.
嗨
Hey.
- 谢谢   - 不 谢谢你 米兰达
- Thank you.     - No, thank you, Miranda.
- 是梅玲达   - 好吧
- Melinda.     - All right.
- 那真的好可爱   - 你在看我们吗
- How cute was that?     - Oh! Were you watching?
- 下一个是我吗   - 嗯…
- Can I go next?     - Uh...
当然是 来吧
Of course you can. Hop on.
好吧 但我要排在她后面
Okay. But I get to hop on after her.
- 我一定能得分   - 什么
- I am so gonna score!     - What?
我喜欢你的蝴蝶结
I like your bow.
我要请大家举杯 向摩妮卡及钱德致意…
I'd like to propose a toast to Monica and Chandler...
他们是全世界最速配的夫妻 也是我最好的朋友
...the greatest couple in the world, and my best friends.
我刚听说他们要结婚时 我有点生气
When I first found out they were getting married, I was a little angry.
我心想"天啊 为什么 你为什么要把他们从我身边抢走"
I was like, "Why, God? How can you take them away from me?!"
然后我回想起我们之间所有的回忆
But then I thought back over our memories together.
快乐的回忆
Some happy memories.
跟悲伤的回忆
Then there were some sad memories.
对不起
I'm sorry.
还有可怕的回忆
And some scared memories. Whoa!
然后我了解到 我永远都会是他们的朋友
And then I realized I'll always be their friend.
他们的朋友能说许多台词…
Their friend who can speak in many dialects...
接受过舞台打斗训练 愿意拍部分裸露的戏
...has training in stage combat and is willing to do partial nudity.
敬这对金童玉女
Oh... To the happy couple.
- 谢谢 那真的是太棒了 艾许莉 - 我们能再跳一次吗
- That was very nice, Ashley.     - Can we do it again?
不行
No, no.
- 现在轮到我了吗    - 我是下一个
- So is it my turn?     - I'm next.
噢
Oh!
- 没关系 你可以先跟她跳   - 你确定
- That's okay, you can dance with her first.     - Are you sure?
好吧
Okay.
- 你叫什么名字    - 葛特
- So what's your name?     - Gert.
很美的名字
That's pretty.
来吧
Come on.
哇 哇
Whoa! Whoa!
你在做什么 葛特
What are you doing, Gert?
跟其他女孩一样 踩在你脚上跳舞
Dancing on your feet like the other girls did it.
好吧
Okay.
跳上来吧 葛特
Hop on, Gert.
- 你的脚为什么不动    - 我在努力了
- Why aren't you moving your feet?     - I'm trying.
快一点 你跳的太慢了
Faster! You're not going fast enough!
或许我该踩在你脚上
Maybe I should stand on your feet!
你有听到我的致词了吗
So did you happen to catch my toast up there?
天啊 你那么做是为了我
Oh, my God. That was for my benefit?
我那么做是为了所有人
Well, I like to think there was something for everyone.
我知道你在为新戏选角
I know you're casting for this new show.
我想你不适合这个计划
Look, Joey, I don't think you're right for it.
你错了 不论内容是什么 我都办得到
See, that's where you're wrong. Whatever it is, I can do it.
如果你对刚刚的表演不满意 考考我
And if you didn't see it up there, just try me.
那出戏的演员全是中国人
It's an all Chinese cast.
你可以变成中国人吗
Can you be Chinese?
- 我不以此为荣 但是…   - 天啊 求求你别那么做
- I'm not proud of this, but...     - Oh, my God. No, please! Don't!
- 准备重回舞池了吗   - 它变成沙地了吗
- Ready to get back on the dance floor?     - Did it turn into sand?
- 我喜欢这首歌 你会跳得很好的   - 不 我不会的
- Come on, I love this song. You'll be fine.     - No, I won't.
你知道为什么我要去上舞蹈课吗
Do you know why I took all those lessons?
我不希望你被看到
For the first time, I didn't want you to be embarrassed...
跟一个笨拙的白痴跳舞 丢光了脸
to be seen on the dance floor with some clumsy idiot.
甜心 你不可能让我出糗
Aww. Sweetie, you could never embarrass me.
好吧 你很容易就会让我出糗
Okay, you could easily embarrass me.
但那不重要 好吗
But it doesn't matter. Right?
我嫁给你
I married you.
我要在我的婚礼和我丈夫跳舞 来吧
So I'm gonna dance on my wedding night with my husband. Come on!
- 尽量不要移动你的脚   - 噢
- Just try not to move your feet at all.     - Oh.
就是那样
There you go.
- 钱德 我要逮捕你   - 为什么
- Chandler, I'm gonna have you arrested.     - Why?
你偷走了我的舞步
You stole my moves.
- 还要多久    - 30秒
- How much longer?     - Thirty seconds.
30秒 好吧…
Thirty seconds. Okay.
我错过了吗
Did I miss it?
瑞秋 我要你知道
Rachel, I want you to know...
如果是阳性反应 我们得…
...that if it's positive, we...
- 我知道   - 你知道 好吧
- I know. I know.     - You do? Okay.
时候到了
It's time.
不准进来
No!
- 来吧 瑞秋   - 等一下 知道吗 我不敢看
- Go ahead, Rach.     - Oh, wait. You know what? I can't look at it.
我不敢看 谁帮我看一下
I can't look at it. Somebody else tell me.
- 好   - 好
- Okay.     - Okay.
是阴性反应
It's negative.
- 什么    - 是阴性反应
- What?     - It's negative.
噢
Oh.
真相揭晓
Well, there you go.
哟
Whew!
那…那真的是太棒了 这真是个天大的好消息
That is... That is really great, great news.
因为这整件事…
Because the whole...
在经济方面我还没有准备好 所以…
...not being ready, the financial aspects, all that...
事情本来就应该是这样的
This is so just the way it was supposed to be.
那么说的话 太棒了
Then, great.
天啊 这真的是太愚蠢了
God. This is so stupid.
我怎么会为了我从来没有拥有过的东西难过
How can I be upset over something I never had?
是阴性反应吗
It's negative?
不 是阳性反应
No, it's positive.
- 什么    - 不是阴性反应 是阳性反应
- What?     - It's not negative, it's positive.
- 你确定    - 对 刚刚我说谎
- Are you sure?     - Yeah, I lied before.
噢
Oh!
喔 我的天
Oh, my God!
- 现在你知道真正的感觉了吧 - 那是个危险的小把戏
- Now you know how you really feel about it.     - Oh! That's a risky little game.
你真的要这么做
Are you really gonna do this?
对 我要生下孩子
Yeah. I'm gonna have a baby.
我要生下孩子
I'm gonna have a baby!
- 孩子的爸是谁    - 不 现在还不是时候
- With who?     - No, it's still not the time.
（谨献给纽约市的人们）
我不知道接下来是快歌
I just didn't see the fast song coming.
别说话 我们送你回房问
Shh. Don't try to talk.
我们送你回房间 让你泡泡脚 你会没事的
We'll get you up to your room, soak your feet. You'll be okay.
- 谢谢   - 那真的是太好心了
- Oh, thank you.     - That is so sweet!
- 是的   - 不 我是认真的
- Yeah.     - No, I mean it.
现在好男人不多了
There's so few genuinely nice guys out there.
你说的对
Tell me about it.
我觉得自己像是死守碉堡的士兵
I feel like I'm holding down the fort all by myself.
- 你是乔伊 对吧    - 对
- It's Joey, right?     - Yeah.
等一下 不 我才是好人
Wait a minute! No! I'm the nice one!
是我整晚跟孩子们跳舞 我…
I'm the one that danced with the kids all night.
你的脚好小喔
How small are your feet?